{
  "collection": {
    "name": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
    "description": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
    "hidden": "false"
  },
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "anneau",
      "back": "prsten",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "botte",
      "back": "bota",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "chapeau",
      "back": "klobouk",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "chaussettes",
      "back": "ponožka",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "chaussure",
      "back": "střevíc, bota",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "chemise",
      "back": "košile",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "col",
      "back": "límec",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "costume",
      "back": "oblečení",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "cravate",
      "back": "kravata, vázanka",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "jupe",
      "back": "sukně",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "manteau",
      "back": "kabát",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "pierre précieuse",
      "back": "skvost, klenot",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "sac",
      "back": "kabelka",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "tissu",
      "back": "látka, tkanina",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "valise",
      "back": "kufr",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "veston",
      "back": "kabát, bunda",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "French - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    }
  ],
  "settings": {
    "id": 1,
    "playVoiceText": "true",
    "languageOfVoice": "fr",
    "typeOfVoice": "f2",
    "volumeOfVoice": 100,
    "displayAnswer": "false",
    "displayAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "limitTAnswer": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTime": 60,
    "showAnswerTime": "false",
    "limitTAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTimeByRepeating": 60,
    "showAnswerTimeByRepeating": "false",
    "filteringCards": "true"
  }
}
